

# Asir Intesar Ibne Zaman

I am a positive and diligent individual with strong organizational skills and exceptional interpersonal abilities. As a passionate data driven product enthusiast, I excel at collecting, validating, and modeling datasets to optimize product performance. I have a knack for market research, feature analysis, and identifying valuable patterns. With a strong belief in the power of determination, I continuously strive for professional growth and achievement of career objectives.





+880 1953608315 M asirintesar97@gmail.com



m www.linkedin.com/in/asirintesar ## https://asirintesar.github.io



# **Work Experience**

### **Associate Product Manager** (Feb 2024-Present) **Myalice**

- Developed product roadmaps to prioritize and manage product development initiatives.
- Coordinated with internal stakeholders to launch products within specified timelines.
- Conducted feature analysis and drafted PRD to drive concrete product growth.
- Fostered cross-functional collaboration among engineering, success, and marketing teams.

## Product Analyst, Sr. Executive (Oct 2022-April 2024) **Bdjobs.com Limited**

- Developed product roadmaps to prioritize and manage product development initiatives.
- Analyzed customer feedback and identified trends to inform product strategy decisions.
- Generated reports on key performance indicators to measure success of current products.
- Facilitated cross-functional collaboration between engineering, marketing, and sales teams.

## **Product Executive** (Jan 2022-Sep 2022) **Adplay Technology Limited**

- Prepared monthly reports highlighting key accomplishments and areas needing improvement.
- Coordinated with internal stakeholders to launch products within specified timelines.
- Drafted detailed business plans outlining financial projections, marketing strategy and pricing models.
- Performed quality assurance tests on all products prior to release into the market place.

# Operation Analyst (Internship) (Oct 2021-Jan 2022) Shopup

 Analyzed data to identify operational trends, issues, and improvement opportunities.

 Collaborated with team to formulate compelling, data-driven solutions to operational issues.

# **Skill & Exepertise**

Tools & Technologies: Jira, Google Analytics, Mixpanel, Microsoft Office, Google Data Studio, PowerBI, Tableau, Adobe XD, Figma, Rstudio.

Industrial Knowledge: Product Management, Data Analysis, UIUX Design, Machine Learning, Agile Methodolies.

Language & Database: Python, R, MySQL, MS Sql Server, Bigquery.

**Soft Skills & Others:** Leadership, Prioritization, Feature Analysis, User Acceptance Testing, Product Requirement

### **Education**

### **Bachelor of Science in Computer Science & Engineering**

**American International University - Bangladesh (AIUB)** 

Jan 2018 - Sep 2021

#### **Awards & Honors:**

Nominated for Best Thesis Award

#### **Extracurricular Activities:**

Photographer and Event Organizer at AIUB Photography Club

### **HSC** in Science

**Dhaka City College** 

2014-2016

### SSC in Science

**Motijheel Govt Boys' High School** 

2005-2014

#### **Awards & Honors:**

Finalist, MGBHS Photography Contest

# **Training & Certification**

- Product Management Career Track | Bohubrihi
- Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate | Coursera
- Emotional Intelligence | Bohubrihi

## **Personal Interest**

- Travelling | Travel vlogs on youtube channel
- Cycling | Got souvenir from Bdcyclist
- Blogging | Writing blogs on data at Medium and LinkedIn, mostly sports
- Aquascaping | Experienced in Planted and Community tank

## Reference

Shafi Mohammad Wasif Osman GM, CLM Innovation & Analytics Robi Axiata Limited

Email: smwosman@gmail.com

Andalib Hasan
Operations Director
Foodpanda

Email: andalib14@gmail.com